(Sheldon:)That's because
I'm not being challenged.
(Sheldon:)It's the same reason
Einstein failed math.
(Amy:)Maybe the math
was too bubbly for him.
(Sheldon:)You think you're doing science
by cutting up that brain?
They could do the same at Quiznos.
(Sheldon:)And they'd offer to toast it for me too.
(Amy:)Okay, smart guy.
(Amy:)I'm about to remove the locus coeruleus,
which is incredibly delicate work.
(Amy:)Have at it.
(Amy:)All right.
(Sheldon:)I'm no stranger to a little gray matter.
(Amy:)Locus coeruleus.
(Amy:)You're getting warmer.
It is indeed in the brain.
(Amy:)Hope your hands are steady.
It's the width of a single hair.
(Amy:)But this is just biology,
so it's no problem for a genius like you.
It's not. I will have you know
in the field of physics we work...
(Sheldon:)...with particles so small they make
fat jokes about the locus coeruleus...